Hey guys, if you haven't subscribed to my newsletter, Beyond the Algorithm,
then please go to amandaseals.com and do so. We're just dropping the newest one
today. Now this newsletter really is not just about promotion, it's also about elevating with
information. So some of the topics that we're talking about in this month's newsletter is
the power of your dollar. We're going to share information on how where you spend money impacts
the country. This of course also comes back to how where we spend money impacts what aid we're
sending to Israel. This also connects to the Fearless Fund and Edward Bloom and what he's
trying to do to take our sisters out of the gang. We also have our Changemaker of the Month. This
month it's House of Palestine down in San Diego. Shout out to Akram, his aunt, his mom, and the
whole team out there who was putting on for Palestine. We got our Watched on Watch, so our
resident film and TV critic from the Amanda Seale Show is going to tell y'all what not to waste your
time on and what to dig into. We also have book recommendations in case you missed it, people
coming on small doses, etc. So go sign up if not for the reason that you don't want to
miss it when I come to your town because your girl is on tour.